Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
When I think back to that day.
small details stick in my mind.
Things I said;
the looks on people's faces.
They wanted to wipe us
from the face of the Earth ...
but we kept asking ourselves.
"Why?"
After all the centuries of
mindless cruelty
maybe we shouldn't have been
surprised
Are we really so different?
There's evil inside of us all.
Yes Sophia. it's me.
You do not answer your phone.
Your sponsor says you don't go
to the meetings any more.
I'm worried about you.
I'm at the observatory tonight.
Please call me. Good day.
Every song in the World
at your fingertips.
I can never decide what to play.
Choice paralysis. I have it when I go to the
hypermarket. There is a hundred different options.
I just want toothpaste.
Have you seen this?
What's the source?
Ross 128.
Can you check the frequency?
153.26 GigaHertZ.
So high? That can't be right.
That's what it says.
-Can you sonify the signal?
Could be a satellite.
I check with the ESA.
No registered satellite in that
band pass.
Is there a pulsar there?
No. there is no pulsar at those coordinates.
And the frequency is too high.
What's that?
The signal that Arecibo
picked up last year.
You know. the one from Ross 128b.
It's the same.
- Yeah. but it's a lot stronger.
So what are we saying?
What is it?
There's no naturally occuring phenomenon
that can produce a signal like this.
Not in that frequency.
Where would you put it on the Rio scale?
-I don't know.
Six. maybe seven.
Put out an ATel.
We need someone else to verify it.
Contact ALMA; ask them to take a look at it.
Hanes.     - Sorry.
And?
ALMA Confirms the signal.
They're getting the same readings; flipping out.
Phase it up again.
Are you really sure it cannot be a pulsar?
I've already checked.
This is real.
What if we're wrong. and we'll look ridiculous.
We're not wrong. Catherine. Make the call.
With Catherine Durand of the Institut
the Radio Astronomy Millimétrique.
I believe we have detected evidence...
of extraterrestrial life.
West London
No way. that is not your breakfast.
-I'm late.
College doesn't start 'til nine.
-I'm meeting some friends.
Okay. take a banana.
-Eating a banana's your answer to everything.
Looks sore.
- You hate it. don't you?
It's your arm.
- Are you going to tell Dad?
Maybe we can wait 'til he gets home.
Go meet your friends.
Why aren't you dressed for school?
- I said I'd call Dad.
Convention Center
North France
Hey buddy. how are you doing?
Is Mom okay?  Yeah?
Yeah. no not now. I can't talk to her now.
I'm just checking in. but tell her I'll call her later. okay?
Alright. okay. yeah. cheers buddy. okay.
Say hello to Em for me. Bye.
Hey. How are you doing?  -Good.
-Good. Madeline Clairmont.
Increasing the amplitude of the
stimulation current
results in the hyper-activation of the
primary somatosensory and pre-motor cortex.
This is direct evidence that an induced
current contributes most to corticospinal
pathway excitation.
So. actually...
Raising the stimulation amplitude
would increase the amounts of neurons firing
and result in a larger response.
as we've just witnessed.
Excuse me. am I boring you?
Maybe we should fire a few neurons
into your brain just to get the juices flowing.
We can make sense of this targeting of diverse
neuronal structures by two half segments.
The signal was detectable for exactly
23 hours and 56 minutes.
One sidereal day. One complete
rotation of the Earth.
Is there any significance in that?
-We don't know.
You part of the METI initiative.
You've been sending messages into space?
We send music.  The idea is that music
would act as a universal language.
but if they don't have ears
they won't be able to hear it.
So. we encoded the entire message
in a binary system of two alternating frequencies
pulsing 125 times  per second.
Could this be a response?
-If it is. it's in a language that we don't understand.
The electromagnetic waves were
transmitted across a vast distance
with virtually no atenuation.
What does that mean?
It means that the power source that generated the signal
is greater than we can even conceive.
Does this mean that they're a threat?
There's no evidence to suggest that.
But surely it would be wrong to assume they
aren't a threat.
Dr. Durand. what do we know?
Two years ago we discovered
an exoplanet orbiting Ross 128.
The planet is in a habitable zone.
and it may be able to support life.
But that's all we know.
Why are we detecting this signal now?
We can't say for sure.
Perhaps they were looking for us.
Thank you.  Perhaps you can leave
us for a minute.
Doctor - I'm Colonel Mokrani.
I am your point of contact.
Pleasant.
How is it going?
You frightened them.
On Wednesday at appromiately
2300 hours Universal Time
Dr. Catherine Durand of the Institut
de Radio Astronomy Millimétrique ...
detected a powerful signal
originating from an area
close to the star Ross 128.
All the evidence suggests that this signal
is indivicative of intelligent extraterrestrial life.
I hope this disovery is something
that will unite the human race.
Perhaps we willl see now that we're
far more alike than we are different.
Hey. what is it?
Ayden.
Tonight. 10pm.
Do you ever go skiing?
Do I ever go skiing?
-Yes.
Because you work in the mountains.
I mean.
I used to.
but it was ages ago.
Is everything alright?
-Yes.
Terrible. this.
My men have secured things. So
rest assured if there's any trouble.
I will do.
Catherine. how did it go in Brussels?
-It was okay.
Can you believe this?
Hi. Dad.
-Oh. hi.
Are you heading off again?
-I'm going to be sleeping at the office while this thing play out.
So. what aren't they telling us?  Should we be concerned?
-Well there's nothing to tell; they detected a signal.
Well. when the government tell you not to panic.
that's when you gotta buy a rifle and head for the hills.
You'd shoot yourself in your foot.
You'll be lying there hoping the evil
goverment comes and rescues you.
You want me to open that?
-Oh. I can open a bottle of wine.
Have you spoken to your Mom?
-She's fine.
Are you in tomorrow night? Jack said
he'd drop by the rest of my stuff.
What am I supposed to say to him?
Well. try nice polite conversation.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
You don't want me to stick on on him
because he dumped you. do you?
Is that supposed to make me feel better?
I'll call you.
-Okay.
You should come out for the product launch.
Vegas is crazy.
Yeah. it's difficult. you know. for me to
be away from home for too long.
Oh. I thought you said your daughter
is coping much better now.
Yes. she is.  She is. but.
-Then come to Vegas.  It will be fun.
Should I get another bottle?
-No. you know what. it's late.
But you could invite me back to your room
Or perhaps it's a bad idea.
Yes sir?
The bill please.
-Coming.
Come on. Sophia. Pick up the telephone.
No. don't take me.
Catherine.
Something's happening.
What is it?
-Multiple objects are approaching the Earth.
What kind of objects?
-No idea.
They are approaching at
more than 1000 kilometers per second.
Impossible.
What?
I can't.
They're slowing down.
Because they're hitting the atmosphere.
Could it...
be an attack?
What's going on?
-No idea. What is that?
What is that?
Is that a meteor?
Eighty seconds left.
Shouldn't we do something?
-Do what?
What the fuck is that?
Emily. what are you doing?
Can't you feel it?
-Get inside.
Ten seconds left.
Six. five. four. three. two ...
Several places have been hit ...
but only in certain areas.
it seems.
I want an update every ten minutes
about the affected places.
Last night's attacks have sent fearful tremors across the globe.
...emergency services are working around the clock to rescue citizens.
Reports suggest upwards of 2.500 objects.
The goverment has responded by declaring a state of emergency.
Schools have been closed. and all civilin
aircraft are grounded until further notice.
Command Post United Kingdom
We're getting reports of rioting in London.
Manchester and Birmingham.
There's severe congestion on all routes out
of major cities. It's only going to get worse.
Oh. we need to get the message out. People should stay
in their own homes - it's the safest place for them to be.
- I'll get on it.
But your family are here.
- It's just a precaution - until things calm down.
Keep me updated.
Bye. sister.
I hope you're unharmed.
I know you don't want to talk ...
just send a message
that all is well.
Please.
Alpha Team. come in.
Radioactivity levels are normal.
Testing negative for chemical
and biological agents.
We're detecting a strong
electromagnetic field.
The image falls away.
-Alpha Team - we've lost visual.
It is some kind of metallic object.
Alpha Team - can you identify?
Alpha Team - come in.
I say. it's partially -
it's buried in the ground.
A spherical. non-porous.
metallic object.
Are you getting this?
Alpha Team. come in.
I repeat- radioactivity levels normal.
Negative chemical and biological agents.
Strong electromagnetic field.
Object...
Metallic. spherical. non-porous.
Partially buried.
Pick up. damn it.
Why do you keep calling me?
We are not liking each other right now.
but come to the observatory.
Why?
It's safer.
Are those things dangerous then?
-I do not know.
Please come here.
Trust me now.
What is going on?
Do you still have gas in your tank?
-Yes. Now say what's up.
Leave everything behind and come here.
-How so? You scare me.
I beg you.
-Okay.
People are getting out of London. so maybe I should
go to my Dad's until we know what's happening.
Yeah. you should. You should go.
The Channel Tunnel is still open.
So let's see if I can get a train.
And I'm going to meet you at Dad's as soon as I can. okay?
Be careful.
-Okay. Bye.
Bill?
-Uh. hi Helen.
I just wanted to check
and see if you're okay.
These things last night -
God. it's insane.
Bill. one of the neighbors saw you having
around the apartment last night.
Jeez. I just passing by. Was it the
crazy old bitch with the shitty dog?
She never liked me.
You know it's her dog that craps in the hallway.
It is not appropriate for you to just show up here.
What is it you want?
What do you think's going to happen with us?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Him again?
I'm going to talk to him.
He's just worried.
It's not his job to worry about you.
The most significant discovery so far
was from astrophysicists in Brazil.
They were the first to observe concentrated
electromagnetic activity in local sources.
Several sources have now confirmed...
There are already four unknown
substances found in it.
What causes
the electromagnetic field?
We only know the frequency
and vibration width are constantly increasing.
We also send space probes to
other planets. It is possible ...
that they are here to do research.
Why would they send so many?
And why only inhabited areas?
The first signal.
It took exactly one day.
Yeah. so?
They must have made a scan.
Have they mapped the Earth?
Do we have to destroy them?
They could be weapons.
- Check the pictures of Wyoming.
Look - an F-16 has bombed one.
Not a scratch.
My parents absolutely want me to be with them.
So. I'll stay if you want me to. of course. but...
You should go.
- Okay. Bye.
Expert analysis indicates the probes
are emitting an electromagnetic field.
Though little is understood of its purpose.
Scientists around the World are caught up in a
fervent debate as to the implications.
but no conclusive answers have been found thusfar.
There is still widespread speculation as to the cause of the dropout in power...
Hey Tony. it's Bill.
Listen Tony. I need the results of your
subretinal stimulation study.
That should be on the shared drive.
On the shared hard drive?
Okay thanks. I'll talk to you later.
Dan. you gotta talk to the minister.
-Dad. slow down.
No. you gotta listen to me Dan. The electromagnetic
fields these probes are emitting - I think it's designed
to interfere with our neural functioning.
They're identical to the pulses we use to stimulate neurons in the brain.
It's the exact same frequency and amplitude - everything.
It's almost like they understand our neurology.
-How is that even possible?
I don't know. But as the pulse gets stronger it's
going to cause more and more neurons to fire; it'll cause seizures.
and our bodies will shut down completely.
-Are you sure?
As sure as I can be.  People need to get somewhere
completely encased in metal. or deep underground.
Dan. you have to get the government
to issue a warning.
Okay. I'll speak to the minister.
He's saying that we'll start to fit. and that our bodies will completely shut down.
Yes. our scientists are saying the same thing.
They've been running tests at Wortendale.
- What? You knew?
Then. we need to issue an alert.
-We can't issue a warning until we're sure; we can't risk mass panic.
What if it's too late.
-Dan. the decision's been made. Okay?  We wait.
Taxi.
To the station please.
-I'm not in service.
Please. come on. I really have to get to the...
-Get out of my taxi.
Look. just take this please. Just go.
Okay. thank you.
They're turning people around.
Then what do we do?
- Maybe we should just go home.
I thought you said it wasn't safe there.
-I'm not sure we've got much choice.
Thigs might calm down later; we can try again.
Text dad - let him know we're going home.
What is that?
Can you feel something?
That's the sound - I heard it last night.
Can't you hear it?
-No.
It's so weird.
Excuse me. is there another route we can take. or?
I have nothing more.
Make sure I get there.
What the fuck is that?
-What is it?
What is that?
The electromagnetic fields
affect the atmosphere.
The British government
warns of an attack.
They're saying there's going to be an attack.
It's the government's Twitter feed.
They're telling people to find shelter. To get underground.
What should we do?
-I don't know.
Mom ...
Why are they shooting at people?
I'm sure they're just firing into the air; they're warning shots.
- Your voice changes when you lie.
With me. Where are you?
-I'm stuck in traffic on the mountain pass.
Listen. We're being attacked.
You must seek cover.
Attacked?
-Just search for underground coverage.
Hurry up.
-I can't go anywhere.
Bill. what are you doing?
-I've got to find Helen.
No. she doesn't want to see you. You know that.
-You don't understand. There's an attack.
You've gotta calm down.
-It's happening. We don't have time.
Mom. What should we do?
Mom. Do something.
Slow down.
What was that?
Why are you going so quickly?
Get out. get out.  Get into the station.
Helen. open up.
Open up.
What are you doing here?
-You've gotta come with me right now.
Come with me right now or you're gonna die.
Come with you where?
To the elevator.  It'll protect us against the electromagnetic field.
Have you seen Chris?
-No I haven't. Get in the elevator now.
We have to find Chris first.
-We don't have time.
What are you doing? Bill! Don't! Chris!
-You've gotta come with me.
Sorry to ruin everything.
-That is not true.
Yes. And you always help me.
-Make sure you go underground.
I have said as much to you.
-Go underground. Right now.
I would not know where.
We have lost contact with our places.
They've crashed.
Something is happening.
What is happening?
Connect quickly.
And seek cover.
How long 'til we get there?
-We have to find a way to get out of the...
Watch out.
Keep all doors closed.
Is it over?
- That is yet to be seen.
People. flashlights out.
Let's save the batteries.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm